Hey! I'm all packed and ready to go.
嘿，我都打包好可以走了
That's right. Daddy and Uncle Joey are going on a trip today.
沒錯，爹地跟喬伊叔叔今天要出門去
We're going to a conference in Barbados. Right? Can you say, "Barbados"?
我們要去參加一個在巴貝多的研討會 你會說「巴貝多」嗎？
Barbados.
巴貝多
Okay. I've gotta say, it means so much to me that you guys are coming..
我覺得要你們 到那麼遠的地方去…
all the way over there to hear me give my speech.
聽我的演講，對我真是意義重大
And I have a surprise. I had to pull some strings..
我讓要你們高興一下 我費盡功夫…
but I was able to get everyone passes to the entire conference. That's right!
幫大家爭取到整個研討會的通行證 沒錯！
These babies will get you into all the paleontology lectures and seminars.
這些寶貝可以讓你們自由參加所有的 古生物學演講或是研討會
Do you have anything that will get us out of them?
你有什麼東西 是可以讓我們不用參加的嗎？
We're excited to hear the speech, but the rest of the time..
我們真的很興奮要聽你的演講 但是其他的時間…
we're gonna want to do island stuff.
我們想要做一些島上活動
David will probably want to hear a few lectures.
大衛或許會想要聽幾場演說
- Right, because he's a scientist. - No, no.
-沒錯，因為他是科學家 -不，不
He's been in Minsk for eight years. If he gets too much direct sunlight..
他在明斯克待了八年 如果他在陽光下太久…
he'll die.
他會死的
- Okay, we'd better go. - Yeah?
-好的，我們最好出發了 -是嗎？
- So we'll see you guys tomorrow. - All right, let's do it.
-那我們明天見 -好的，明天見
A five-hour flight with Charlie, have a couple drinks..
跟查莉一起飛行五個小時，喝幾杯酒…
get under that blanket and do what comes natural.
在毛毯下做一些自然會發生的事
It's a blanket, Joe, not a cloak of invisibility.
那是毛毯，喬伊，不是隱形大衣
The One In Barbados
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
- Wow, this place is beautiful! - Look at all these paleontologists!
-哇，這地方真漂亮！ -瞧瞧這些古生物學家！
I know. There are gonna be some pasty folks by the pool tomorrow.
我知道 明天游泳池旁一定有許多蒼白的人
- My God, I can't believe you're here! - I think I've been recognized.
-我的天啊，我不敢相信你在這裡！ -我想我被認出來了
- This happens all the time. - Dr. Geller? I am such a huge fan.
-這常常發生的 -蓋勒博士？我真是仰慕你
That never happens.
這倒是從來沒有發生過
I've been following your career for years. I can't wait for your keynote speech.
我多年以來一直很注意你的研究 我等不及要聽你的演說了
- Wow! This is very flattering. - I would love your autograph.
-哇，你太過獎了 -我會很想要你的簽名的
Well, sure.
喔，當然
- "Dear..?" - Sarah.
-親愛的？ -莎拉
"Sarah. I dig you."
「莎拉，我挖（喜歡）你」
- "Dr. Ross Geller." - Oh, thank you so much.
-「羅斯蓋勒博士上」 -哇，真是太謝謝你了
Sure. Sarah, I'd like you to introduce you to my colleague, Professor Wheeler.
不客氣，莎拉，讓我幫你介紹一下 我同事，魏勒教授
- And this is Joey Tribbiani. - Are you a paleontologist?
-這位是喬伊崔比亞尼 -你是古生物學家嗎？
No, God, no, no. I'm an actor.
不，天啊，不，我是演員
You probably recognize me from a little show called The Days of Our Lives.
你或許有看過我演的一出小戲叫做 《那個我們的日子》
Dude, it's just Days of Our Lives. There's no "the."
老兄，只是《我們的日子》 沒有「那個」
Okay, Ross. Boy, you.. Yeah. No, no. I play Dr. Drake Ramoray.
好的，羅斯，天啊，你…是啊 不，我扮演德克羅曼瑞醫生
- I'm sorry. I don't own a TV. - You don't own a TV?
-我很抱歉，我家沒有電視 -你家沒有電視？
What's all your furniture pointed at?
那你家的家俱是擺向哪個方向呢？
- Well, it was a pleasure to meet you all. - You too, Sarah.
-很榮幸認識你們 -我們也是，莎拉，再見
Jeez, who doesn't own a TV?
天啊，這年頭誰沒有電視呢？
Well, actually, I don't.
嗯，事實上，我沒有
Yeah, and mine broke two months ago and I still haven't gotten a new one.
是啊，我的兩個月前壞了 還沒買新的
Well, didn't you two come to the right convention.
那你們兩個還真是來對研討會了
David, can you help me?
大衛，你可以幫個忙嗎？
I'm trying to explain to Chandler how a plane stays in the air.
我正在跟錢德解釋 飛機是怎麼漂浮在空中的
Certainly. That's a combination of Bernoulli's Principle..
當然，那是波諾利原理加上…
- and Newton's third law of motion. - See?
-牛頓第三運動定律 -知道了嗎？
Yeah. That's the same as, "It has something to do with wind."
是啊，那還真是跟 「跟風有關的」一樣
I'm gonna go pick up a few things for the trip.
我要去為這次旅行買幾樣東西
I should go too. Now, tomorrow do you want to share a cab to the airport..
我也應該走了 明天你們要一起搭計程車到機場嗎？
or should Mike and I meet you?
還是說我跟麥克到機場跟你們碰面呢？
Mike? Who's Mike?
麥克？誰是麥克呢？
- Mike's your ex-boyfriend. - That's right!
-麥克是你的前男友 -沒錯！
Oh, yeah. Wow, I had totally forgotten about him.
哇，我已經完全忘了他了
- That's a blast from the past, huh? - No, it's okay. Honest mistake.
-難忘往日情懷脫口而出嗎？ -不，沒關係的，無心之過
It really doesn't mean anything. I mean, you know..
那真的不代表什麼 我是說，你知道的…
Monica refers to Chandler as Richard all the time.
摩妮卡也常常把錢德叫成李察
- She does? - Let's get you out of here.
-她有嗎？ -我們快讓你離開吧
Well, at least you took me down with you.
至少你也拖我下水了
I'm so sorry. I just.. I keep thinking about Mike.
我很抱歉，我只是… 我一直在想麥克
I'm crazy about David, and we're having so much fun together.
我非常喜歡大衛 而且我們在一起很開心
Why? Why do I miss Mike? That's just.. That's gonna go away, right?
為什麼我會想念麥克？這真是… 這會消逝的，對嗎？
- Well, I guess. In time. - Yeah.
-嗯，我猜是吧，總有一天 -是啊
I mean, my feelings for Richard are certainly gone.
我是說我對李察的感覺 都已經消失了
You just did it again. Chandler. Your feelings for Chandler are certainly gone.
你又來了，是錢德 你對錢德的感覺都已經消失了
Boy, Phoebe's still pretty hung up on that Mike, huh?
天啊，菲比還在想麥克嗎？
I wouldn't read too much into it.
我不會想太多的
Still, a girl calls you by her ex-boyfriend's name..
但是女生把你叫成 她前男友的名字…
- that's not a good thing, right? - Let me stop you there.
-那不是什麼好事，不是嗎？ -讓我先打斷你一下
Because I think I see where this is going. I'm not very good at giving advice.
因為我想我知道這是怎麼回事了 我對給人建議不太行
See, if you want advice, go to Ross or Monica. Or Joey..
如果你想知道披薩的餡料或是 為何尿尿時有灼熱感之類的…
for advice about pizza toppings or a burning sensation when you pee.
建議，那就去找羅斯或是 摩妮卡或是喬伊
I'm sorry, I just wish there was something I could do, you know?
很抱歉，我只是希望能做點什麼 你知道嗎？
- Well, you know Phoebe.. - Seriously, we're gonna do this?
-嗯，你知道菲比… -真的，我們要這樣嗎？
I'm sorry, I just wish I could make her forget about Mike already.
很抱歉，我只希望我能讓她忘了麥克
- Why did Phoebe and Mike break up? - Because his penis was too big.
-菲比跟麥克為什麼分手呢？ -因為他的老二太大了
I'm sorry. That's the kind of thing I do.
抱歉，那才是我擅長的事
They broke up because Mike didn't want to get married.
他們分手是因為麥克不想要結婚
What if you let Phoebe know you'd be open to marriage?
如果讓菲比知道 你對婚姻沒有異議呢？
That's great. That's great. I'll propose to her.
太棒了，太棒了，我會跟她求婚
What?
什麼？
I was probably going to do it at some point.
反正我遲早都會這麼做的
- No, I didn't mean now. - Well, why not? It's brilliant.
-不，我沒有說現在 -為何不呢？這實在太聰明了
"Goodbye, Mike. We'll see you at the wedding, fella.
再見，麥克，我們婚禮見，老兄
Well, we probably won't invite you to the wedding, but.."
我們可能也不會 邀請你參加婚禮，但是…
- Well, thank you, Chandler. Sincerely. - Well, you're welcome.
-衷心地謝謝你，錢德 -不用客氣
Glad I could help.
很高興能夠幫得上忙
- How do you think I should propose? - I'm pretending to read here.
-你認為我該怎麼求婚呢？ -我在假裝閱讀
I'm sorry.
抱歉
Yeah. How you doing? Hey, how are you?
你好嗎？嘿，你好嗎？
You said you were gonna wear a thong. Where's the thong?
你說你要穿丁字褲的，丁字褲呢？
I didn't mean a thong. I meant thongs.
我不是說丁字褲 我是說夾腳涼鞋
You really should have been more clear about that.
你應該要說清楚的
You're never gonna guess who I just saw downstairs.
你們不會相信我在樓下看到誰
Britney Spears!
小甜甜布蘭妮！
Yeah. She never misses these conferences.
是啊，她從來不會錯過 這些研討會的
- No, I just saw Dr. Kenneth Schwartz! - Oh, my God!
-我剛剛看到肯尼斯史華茲博士！ -喔，我的天啊！
- I know! - Did you talk to him?
-我知道 -你有跟他說話嗎？
Oh, yeah. What am I gonna say to Kenneth Schwartz?
是喔，我要跟 肯尼斯史華茲說什麼呢？
You could say, "Hey, Kenny, how come you're not Britney Spears?"
你可以說「嗨，肯尼 為什麼你不是小甜甜布蘭妮呢？」
- You ready to go? - You're gonna go now?
-你準備好要走了嗎？ -你現在就要走了嗎？
- I thought we could hang out. - I can't. I have seminars all day.
-我以為我們可以在一起度過 -我不行，我整天都有研討會
I promised Ross I'd look at his speech.
我答應羅斯我會看看他的演說稿
But maybe we could have dinner later? Out on the balcony? It'll be romantic.
但是或許我們晚點可以共進晚餐 在陽台外面，會很浪漫的
Will you wear a thong?
你可以穿丁字褲嗎？
I will if you will.
你穿我就穿
You got yourself a very weird deal.
你的交換條件真是奇怪
I'm good. I have dinner plans.
我很好，我晚餐已經有安排了
- So you gonna be okay? - Yeah, yeah.
-你一個人可以嗎？ -是的，可以
I got tons of stuff I could do. I'm gonna hit the beach, go swimming.
我有很多事可以做 我要去海灘，去游泳
Joe, have you looked outside?
喬伊，你有看看外面嗎？
No. Why?
沒有，為什麼呢？
- Oh, man. - There's an indoor pool.
-天啊 -這裡有室內游泳池
- You could swim there. - Yeah.
-你可以在那邊游泳 -是啊
I wasn't gonna swim. I was gonna dig a hole.
我沒有要游泳，我是要去挖洞的
That Mike thing was interesting. I don't know what's gonna happen..
麥克那件事真是有趣，我不知道…
- with Phoebe and David. - I do. Want a hint, huh?
-菲比跟大衛之間會發生什麼事 -我知道，想要個提示嗎？
I do.
我願意
Okay, I'm sensing this is some kind of wordplay..
好的，我可以感到 這是什麼文字遊戲的
because you are pink with barely controlled glee.
因為你已經有點 無法控制的興奮發紅了
- David's gonna propose to Phoebe. - What? Why?
-大衛要跟菲比求婚了 -什麼？為什麼？
Because we were talking about ways he could beat Mike..
因為我們本來在談 有哪些他可以贏過麥克的方式
and I told him Phoebe wanted to get married.
而我告訴他菲比想要結婚
Chandler, we have talked about this.
錢德，我們已經談過了
You are not supposed to give people advice!
你不可以給別人建議的！
Couldn't you have made some inappropriate joke?
你不能說一些什麼 不適宜的笑話就好了嗎？
I did!
我說了！
A penis one!
一個老二的笑話！
Just so I know, what was so wrong about what I said?
說明一下，我說的有什麼不對的呢？
They've only been going out for a few weeks.
他們才交往幾個星期而已
Phoebe is completely hung up on Mike. I mean, she'll say no..
菲比還無法忘記麥克 我想她會拒絕的
David's heart will be broken, it'll be too hard for them to recover..
然後大衛的心會碎 他們會很難復合
and then Phoebe will end up alone again.
而然後菲比又會是孤單的一個人
Man, that's some bad advice.
天啊，真是糟糕的建議
Oh, hey. Thank God. You guys are here.
感謝上帝你們來了
- What's going on? - Everything is upside-down here.
-怎麼了？ -這裡的一切都不對勁
It rains all day long and nobody watches TV, and Ross is famous.
整天都在下雨，沒有人看電視 而且羅斯還很有名氣
I don't want to alarm anybody..
我不想要驚動大家…
but Monica's hair is twice as big as it was when we landed.
但是摩妮卡的頭髮 比下飛機時大了一倍
Okay. When I go places with high humidity..
好了，當我去高濕度地區的時候…
it gets a little extra body, okay?
頭髮就會比較蓬鬆，好嗎？
That's why our honeymoon photos look like me and Diana Ross.
那就是為什麼我們的蜜月照 看起來是我跟戴安娜羅絲
I'll show you guys where to check in.
我帶你們去登記住房
Oh, honey? Can you make sure we get a king-size bed?
親愛的，你可以確定我們可以拿到 超大尺寸的床嗎？
Oh, David, get one for us too. Oh, and see if they have a heart-shaped one.
大衛，也幫我們確定一下 還有看看他們有沒有心型的床
And with mirrors on the ceiling.
而有天花板上要有鏡子
And make sure our room isn't next to theirs.
還有確定我們的房間 不要在他們的隔壁
Oh, you guys are so lucky you're here with people.
喔，你們真幸運 有人陪你們到這裡
I'd love to share this with someone.
我真想跟某人分享這一切
Oh, honey, you have us. We love you.
親愛的，你有我們，我們愛你
Okay, which one of you is gonna sleep with me?
太好了，你們誰要跟我睡？
You know, it's just such a romantic place.
這是個很浪漫的地方
I just wish I could share it with a guy.
我只希望可以跟一個男人共度
- Not Joey. - Not Joey. No.
-不是喬伊 -不是喬伊，不是
- I was just lusting after Chandler. - Yeah, right.
-我只是在垂涎錢德 -是啊，沒錯
So.. I'm proposing to Phoebe tonight.
我今晚要跟菲比求婚了
Tonight?
今晚？
Isn't an engagement ring supposed to have a diamond?
訂婚戒指不是應該要有鑽石的嗎？
Oh, there it is.
喔，在這裡
Yes, well, being a failed scientist doesn't pay quite as well as you might think.
是啊，一個失敗的科學家 並沒有你想的賺的多
That's one-seventieth of a carat.
那是七十分之一克拉
And the clarity is quite poor.
清晰度是很差
Nice.
很好
- Monica, can I talk to you for a second? - Okay.
-摩妮卡，我可以跟你談一下嗎？ -好的
David's gonna propose to Phoebe tonight.
大衛要在今晚跟菲比求婚
See what happens when you give people advice?
瞧瞧這就是你給別人建議的後果
- Well, I hope you told him not to. - That would be advice!
-我希望你有告訴他不可以 -那又會是一個建議了！
Okay, fine. I'll handle this.
好的，沒關係，讓我來處理
- Phoebe? - Yeah?
-菲比？ -怎樣？
- I need to talk to you. - Are you leaving the Supremes?
-我需要跟你談談 -你要離開你的主宰了嗎？
Okay, my husband just gave your boyfriend some very bad advice.
我老公剛給了你男友 一個很糟糕的建議
David's gonna propose to you tonight.
大衛今晚要跟你求婚了
Wow, really?
哇，真的嗎？
That's fantastic!
這實在太棒了！
What? Are you serious? You want to marry him?
什麼？你是說真的嗎？你想嫁給他？
- What about Mike? - Oh, okay, you want me to marry Mike?
-那麥克呢？ -好的，你要我嫁給麥克是嗎？
Let's just gag him and handcuff him..
讓我們把他塞住嘴巴 用手銬銬住他
and force him down the aisle, okay?
然後逼他踏上紅毯，好嗎？
I can just see it. "Mike, do you take Phoebe?"
我已經可以預見到 「麥克，你願意娶菲比嗎？」
You know? It's every girl's dream.
你知道嗎？真是每個女孩的夢想
Do you really think marrying someone else is the right answer?
你真的認為嫁給別人是對的？
Sure. Look, okay, bottom line? I love Mike.. David!
當然，聽著，最重要的是 我愛麥克…大衛！
David! I love David.
大衛！我愛大衛！
Don't look at me that way, Roseanne Roseannadanna.
別那樣看我，戴安娜羅絲
"By using CT scans and computer imaging, we can, in a very real way..
借由使用中央標準掃瞄法跟電腦影像 我們可以以非常真實的方式…
bring the Mesozoic Era into the 21st century."
將中生代時期帶進二十一世紀
It's great.
太棒了
Yeah, you really think so?
你真的這麼認為嗎？
You'll be the hit of the conference.
你將成為此次研討會的焦點
It'll be even better tomorrow..
明天還會更好
because I won't be constantly interrupted by Joey..
因為我不會一直被喬伊打斷…
checking to see if they put chocolates on my pillow yet.
一直來檢查我枕頭上 是不是有放巧克力
- Hey, guys. - The chocolates aren't here.
-你們好 -巧克力還沒送來
Damn it!
該死的！
Ross just read me his speech. It's fantastic.
羅斯剛念了他的演講稿給我聽 真是精彩
Oh, is it on the computer? Because I'd love to give it a read.
在電腦裡面嗎？因為我也想讀讀看
If you want to check your e-mail, just ask.
如果你想要查電子郵件就說吧
What? May I?
什麼？我可以嗎？
What's with the rain, Geller? I mean, when I signed up for dino week..
那個雨是怎麼回事呢？蓋勒 我是說當我報名恐龍營的時候…
nobody said anything about it being monsoon season.
沒有人說過現在是雨季
- The wet season is June to December. - It's not the time, Charlie.
-雨季是六月到十二月 -現在不是時候，查莉
Oh, no. No, no! Dear God, no!
哎呀，糟糕！親愛的上帝，不！
What, did someone outbid you for the teapot?
怎麼了？有人搶先你標下茶壺嗎？
Secret teapot.
秘密茶壺
Your computer. I don't know what.. Everything's gone.
你的電腦，我不知道怎麼… 一切都不見了
- What do you mean? - Must be a virus.
-你是什麼意思呢？ -一定是病毒
I think it erased your hard drive.
我想它把你的硬碟全殺掉了
What? Oh, my God. What did you do?
什麼？我的天啊！ 你幹了什麼好事？
Someone I don't know sent me an e-mail and I opened it.
一個我不認識的人寄了封信給我 然後我打開了它
- Why? Why would you open it? - Well, it didn't say, "This is a virus."
-為什麼？為什麼你要打開？ -那上面又沒有寫「這是病毒」
- What did it say? - "Nude.."
-那上面寫什麼？ -「裸體的…」
"Pictures of Anna Kournikova."
「安娜庫妮可娃的照片」
- I'm so sorry. - What am I gonna do?
-我很抱歉 -我該怎麼辦呢？
- My speech is gone! - It's not gone.
-我的講稿不見了！ -沒有不見
I'm sure you printed out a copy. You have a hard copy?
我相信你有列印出來，你有印出來嗎？
No, I don't!
不，我沒有！
Well, you must be pretty mad at yourself right now.
那你現在一定很氣自己
- It's really gone? - Yep.
-真的不見了嗎？ -是的
I'd like to thank you guys for coming down here..
我想要謝謝你們過來這裡…
to complain about the rain and ruin my career.
抱怨這些雨 然後毀了我的事業前途
- I just feel awful. - Yeah, you should.
-我覺得糟透了 -你的確應該
Nude pictures of Anna Kournikova? She's never even won a major tournament.
安娜庫妮可娃的裸照？ 她根本連什麼大獎都沒贏過
Well, I tried Billie Jean King, but..
我是有試過比莉珍金，但是…
You know, you and Monica have the same I'm-gonna-kill-you look.
你知道嗎？你跟摩妮卡一樣都有那種 我想要殺死你的表情
I can usually make it go away by kissing her.
我通常可以親她一下 就逃過一劫
Get out.
滾出去
You know, this happens all the time to my computer at work.
我工作的電腦也常常發生這種事
- What do you do? - I usually go..
-那你怎麼辦呢？ -我通常會…
play Tetris on somebody else's computer.
到別人的電腦上 玩俄羅斯方塊
I can't believe this is happening.
我不敢相信發生這種事
I have to give the keynote speech tomorrow.
我明天就要演講了
I have to stand up in front of all these people. What am I gonna say?
我要站在所有人面前，我要說什麼呢？
You can use a speech I memorized for auditions.
你可以用我背下來 參加試演的那段話
I don't think your monologue from Star Wars is gonna help me right now.
我不認為你在《星際大戰》裡的獨白 可以對我有所幫助
Ross, we can solve this. I just heard your speech.
羅斯，不會有問題的 我聽過你的演講
- We can re-create it. We've got all night. - What, you really think we can do that?
-我們可以重建它，我們有一整晚 -什麼？你真的認為我們辦得到嗎？
Oh, wait. Joey and I are supposed to have dinner.
等等，喬伊跟我應該要共進晚餐的
Don't worry about that. I mean, Ross needs you.
別擔心，我知道羅斯需要你
Rachel and I will stay and help any way we can.
瑞秋跟我會留下來盡量幫忙
All right. Okay, let's do it.
好的，我們來開始吧
Well, I know we start by discussing the shortcomings of carbon dating.
我知道我們一開始 是討論碳年代測定法的缺點
And then I move on to what is clearly the defining moment..
然後我接著解說很明顯地什麼是…
of the Mesozoic Era, the breakup of Pangaea. Hello?
中生代的決定時刻，原始大陸的分裂 不是嗎？
And then there's the overview of the Triassic.
然後接下來是三疊紀的概觀
Any chance any of this happened in a galaxy far, far away?
有可能這一切都是在 很遠的銀河發生的嗎？
- Hello? - Okay, Mike?
-哈囉？ -好了，麥克？
Enough is enough. You love Phoebe, and she loves you.
鬧夠了，你愛菲比，而她也愛你
So get over your I-never-wanna-get-married thing..
所以不要再說什麼 不想要結婚的話了
and step up!
趕快站出來！
Who is this?
你是誰？
This is Monica, Phoebe's friend.
我是摩妮卡，菲比的朋友
Sure, Monica. So good to have you back in my life.
摩妮卡，你又回到我生命中 真是太好了
Listen, Phoebe is back with David.
聽著，菲比跟大衛復合了
He's gonna propose, and she's gonna say yes..
他即將要求婚，而她將會答應
but I know she really wants to be with you.
但是我知道 她真正想要的是跟你在一起
He's gonna propose?
他要求婚了？
I'm sorry, did you say something? I can't hear through all this damned hair!
很抱歉，你說什麼呢？ 該死的頭髮遮住我聽不到！
If Phoebe wants to marry David, she should.
如果菲比想要嫁給大衛，那就去吧
I'm not gonna stand in the way of that. Neither should you.
我不會從中作梗，你也不應該
You don't tell me what to do. I tell you what to do.
你不用告訴我該怎麼做 我來告訴你怎麼做
Just call her. She's at the Paradise Hotel in Barbados.
打電話給她，她在巴貝多的天堂飯店
And while I've got you, you've got curly hair.
對了，你也有卷髮
What do you do in the humidity?
在濕氣重的地方你怎麼辦呢？
Damn it!
該死的！
- Well, I hope you're happy. - I hope you're happy too, honey.
-嗯，我希望你很快樂 -我也希望你很快樂
Phoebe's going to say yes to David.
菲比會答應大衛的求婚
- That's what happens when you meddle. - Phoebe's gonna say yes? That's great.
-這就是你愛管閒事的結果 -菲比要答應？太棒了
No, it's not. She's still in love with Mike.
不，一點也不，她還愛著麥克
- There's no chance that will work? - No, I called.
-那不會有什麼結果的嗎？ -沒有，我已經打過電話了
- It's not gonna happen. - Meddler! Meddler!
-不會發生的 -雞婆！雞婆！
If you hadn't meddled to start with..
如果你不先多管閒事…
then I wouldn't have had to go in and meddle myself.
那我就不用插手進來管事了
No matter how much we meddle, we'll never be able to unmeddle..
不管我們插手多深 我們都沒有辦法補救…
the thing that you meddled up in the first place!
你一開始多管閒事惹出來的禍！
This vacation sucks!
這場假期真是爛！
（歡迎古生物學家們）
I'm so bored.
我好無聊
Stupid rain. We can't do anything.
愚蠢的雨，我們什麼都做不了
Well, I brought some books. We could read.
我帶了些書來，我們可以閱讀
Hey, it hasn't come to that yet.
嘿，還沒糟糕到那個地步
Hey, hey, hey, don't mind if I do.
嘿，等一下
I'm sorry, sir, these are for the pharmaceutical convention.
對不起，先生，這些是給藥學研討會的
You feel like going to a convention?
你想要去參加研討會嗎？
- We can't. We're not pharmacists. - I know we're not..
-我們不行，我們不是藥劑師 -我知道我們不是…
but Frank Madaio and Eva..
但是法蘭克馬迭歐跟伊娃齊羅歐…
溫芭還是…
- Kate Miller. - Kate Miller it is.
-凱特米勒 -就是凱特米勒
- Okay. - Oh, good..
-好的 -喔，很好…
And that's the most sex I'm gonna have this weekend.
而這將是我這週末 僅能有的性了
Well, in that case, should I make sure it's on real good?
如果是這樣 我應該確定它黏的夠牢嗎？
Thank you.
謝謝你
So, Kate..
那麼，凱特…
how's the pharmacy game treating you?
藥局這一行好玩嗎？
Well, Frank, I tell you, it's rough.
嗯，法蘭克，我告訴你，很難喔
I mean, is it me or is doctors' handwriting getting harder and harder to read?
我是說，是我的問題還是說醫生寫的字 都越來越難讀了呢？
I know, I know.
我知道，我知道
I tell you.
我告訴你
But on the plus side, we get to wear those white coats..
但是好處是 我們可以穿那些白色外衣…
- and stand behind that really tall counter. - Oh, that's true.
-然後站在非常高的櫃檯後面 -對，是沒錯
You're Joey Tribbiani from Days of Our Lives.
你是《我們的日子》裡的喬伊崔比亞尼
Finally, someone recognizes me. Okay.
終於有人認出我了
And it's The Days of Our Lives.
是《那是我們的日子》
- Jackie, it is him. - Yeah, Jackie, it's me. Come on over.
-賈姬，是他 -是的，賈姬，是我，過來吧
Oh, my God, this is so exciting!
天啊，這真是大驚喜！
So why are you here?
你為什麼會在這裡呢？
I'm doing research for a role in a new movie about pharmacists.
我正在研習一部 關於藥劑師電影的新角色
Yeah, it's called Prescription for Love.
是的，片名叫《愛的處方》
- Nice. - Yeah.
-很好 -是的
This is my friend Rachel. She's in the movie too.
這是我朋友瑞秋 她也有在這電影中演出
I'm an actress.
我是女演員
So, what's the movie about?
電影內容是什麼呢？
Well, I play the handsome, macho pharmacist..
我扮演英俊有男子氣概的藥劑師
and Rachel is my student..
而瑞秋是我的學生
who wants to learn all about..
她想要學習一切關於…
pharmacing.
-藥學的知識 -對
And, see, I'm shy at first..
而且我一開始是很害羞的…
but then, I take off my glasses and become sexy, you know.
但是然後我把眼鏡拿掉 然後變得很性感，知道吧
And there's some nudity, but it's very tastefully done.
然後有一些裸露戲，但是是很有格調的
My nudity in the film is not tasteful at all.
我在劇中的裸露可是一點都沒有格調
So you're doing research?
所以你們是在做研究？
- Do you have any questions for us? - I sure do.
-你對我們有什麼問題嗎？ -我當然有
Where'd that guy get the big, pink drink?
那個人是去哪拿的 那個大杯粉紅色的飲料？
Oh, and then you said that thing about bringing the Mesozoic Era..
喔，然後你開始談將中生代世紀…
into the 21st century.
帶到二十一世紀
Well, yeah. That's it?
對，就這樣嗎？
That's it. That's the whole speech.
這就是整份演講稿
- Yeah. - Oh, my God. We did it.
-是的 -天啊，我們辦到了
Actually, I did it, Ross. You remembered shockingly little of your own speech.
事實上是我辦到了，羅斯 你對自己演講稿的記憶真是少到驚人
Yes, but I did make a pyramid out of the bath products.
是的，但是我倒是用沐浴產品 做了個金字塔
Oh, this is amazing. Thank you. Thank you so much.
這真是驚人，謝謝，真是很謝謝你
That's a pretty necklace.
這真是漂亮的項鏈
Thank you.
謝謝
Hey, what do you say we celebrate? Champagne?
我們慶祝一下吧？要香檳嗎？
Yeah! Save the cork, and that way, we can fill the bottle with water..
好啊，軟木塞留著，這樣我們就可以 把瓶子裝滿水…
and put it back so they don't charge you.
然後再放回去他們就不會收錢了
Oh, my God, I love you.
我的天啊，我愛你
This is such a cute picture of Emma. And is this your son..
艾□這張照片真是可愛 而這是你兒子…
or just some kid whose picture you bring on vacation?
還是你會帶在身上 某個小男孩照片呢？
That's Ben, my son from my first marriage.
那是班，我第一次婚姻所生的兒子
- Your first marriage? - Yeah.
-你第一次婚姻？ -是的
You've been married more than once?
你結過不只一次婚嗎？
No.
沒有
So why'd you break up?
那你為什麼離婚呢？
Oh, it was..
嗯，因為…
It's complicated, you know? She was..
很複雜的，她是…
gay.
同性戀
Actually, it's not that complicated.
事實上並沒有這麼複雜
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
This is so cool!
這實在太酷了！
Okay. Odd thing to get excited about.
好的，為這怪事興奮是很奇怪的事
No, it's just that I was engaged to a guy who turned out to be gay.
不是，只是我曾經跟一個男的訂婚過 而他最後竟然是同志
Hey! High-five!
嘿，擊掌吧！
Didn't you feel so stupid that you didn't see the signs?
你有沒有覺得 沒有看出端倪實在是很笨呢？
My fiance was always going on long weekends with his "tennis partner."
我未婚夫總是跟 他的「網球球友」一起度週末
My wife had a workout friend she went to the gym with every day for a year.
我老婆有年跟一個朋友 天天都到健身房健身
She didn't get any fitter.
她也沒有變瘦
- Everybody's like, "I knew all along." - I know.
-每個人都說「我早就知道了」 -我知道
If you knew, why didn't you tell me? I mean, call, leave a note.
如果知道，怎麼不告訴我呢？ 我是說只要打電話，留個紙條什麼的
"Hi. Just dropped by to say your wife's gay."
「嗨，只是過來告訴你 你老婆是同性戀」
- I know. - And then..
-我知道 -然後…
And then you try to make the best of a bad situation..
然後你試著在困境中求生存…
so you float the idea of a threesome.
所以你提出三人行的建議
I didn't do that.
我沒有那樣做
Me neither.
我也沒有
Well, who knew? Pharmacists are fun.
誰會知道呢？藥劑師們真好玩
I know. That old lady at the end was ready to take you home.
我知道，那位老太太 最後都已經準備要帶你回家了
Not enough pills in the world, Rach.
這世界的藥還是不夠的，瑞秋
What about you, huh? You're the single one. See anybody in there you like?
那你呢？你才是單身的人 有沒有看到喜歡的人呢？
Well, let's see. There was that really big guy that I was talking to..
讓我想想 那個跟我說過話的大個兒…
with the really nice breasts.
有著很不錯的胸部
But what about back home? Anything going on there? Anybody you like?
那在家鄉呢？ 有什麼嗎？你有喜歡的人嗎？
No.
沒有
- There is. You're blushing. - No, I'm not blushing..
-有的，你臉紅了 -沒有，我沒有臉紅
and I'm sunburned.
這是曬傷的
From, you know, the rain.
因為下雨的緣故
You like someone. Tell me who.
你喜歡某人，告訴我是誰
- Tell me who it is. Come on. - No. Joey.
-告訴我是誰，說啦 -不，喬伊
Who do you like? You're not getting away that easy.
你喜歡誰呢？你別想輕易躲掉
- Who do you like? - Joey, come on!
-你喜歡誰呢？ -喬伊，別這樣
It doesn't matter, you know? It's not like anything's gonna happen.
沒什麼大不了的，你知道嗎？ 又不是說會發生什麼事
What? Why not? Rach, who can you not get?
什麼？為什麼不呢？ 瑞秋，有誰你得不到呢？
Okay. Okay. You really want to know who it is?
好，你真想知道是誰嗎？
- Yeah. Who is it? - Do you?
-是的，是誰呢？ -你真的想？
- Oh, hey. - I just left you a message.
-嗨  -我才剛留言給你
Ross and I were gonna go grab a bite..
羅斯跟我剛要去吃點東西…
but now that you're here, we could have that dinner.
但是既然你在這裡 我們可以共用晚餐了
Right! Of course. Hey, did you guys finish the speech?
沒錯！當然 演講稿寫完了嗎？
Yep! We got it. We got it. Thank you so much.
是的，完成了 我們完成了，非常謝謝
- I had a great time. - Yeah.
-我很愉快 -是啊
This isn't over, because I really want to know..
這還沒完，因為我真的想知道…
Later. Later.
等一下，等一下
- So shall we? - Yeah.
-那我們走吧？ -好的
- Okay. - Good night.
-好的 -晚安
Good night.
晚安
- Okay, good night. - Good night, Ross.
-好的，晚安 -晚安，羅斯
I can't believe she's gonna say yes to David.
我不敢相信她會答應
She's clearly in love with Mike.
她很明顯還是愛著麥克
You know, it's very hard to take you seriously when you look like that.
你看起來這樣子 實在很難把你的話當真
Could we have a bottle of champagne, please?
我們可以點瓶香檳嗎？
And I'm kind of on a budget, so if you have anything local..
我手頭有點緊，所以有沒有本地…
or Canadian.
或是加拿大的香檳就可以了
Phoebe, I have something I want to say.
菲比，我要說一些話
Oh, God, he's gonna do it. I cannot watch this. Let's go.
天啊，他要開口了 我看不下去，我們走
I think we have time. Have you heard him talk?
我想我們還有時間 你有聽過他說話嗎？
"Phoebe, I would be honored if.." Spit it out, David!
「菲比，我將會很榮幸如果…」 說快點，大衛
Phoebe.
菲比
You're an amazing woman, and the time we spent apart was unbearable.
你實在是太好了，我們分開的時候 實在無法讓人忍受
Of course, the sanitation strikes in Minsk didn't help.
當然明斯克衛生設施員工的 罷工讓情況更糟
Sure. Okay. Yeah.
當然，好的，是的
But, well, now that we're together again, I don't ever want to be apart.
但是現在我們又一起了 我再也不想分開了
So to that end..
所以…
- Oh, my God, Mike. - It's David, actually.
-喔，我的天啊，麥克 -事實上，我是大衛
No, Mike's here.
不，麥克在這裡
Oh, hey, Mike.
嘿，麥克
Hi, David.
嗨，大衛
Chandler. Monic.. Oh!
錢德，摩妮… 哇！
It's the humidity!
是濕氣！
- Hi, Phoebe. - What are you doing here?
-嗨，菲比 -你在這裡做什麼呢？
I have a question I need to ask you.
我有個問題必須要問你
I have a question I was kind of gonna ask her myself.
我也有個問題要問她
Yeah, I understand, but before you do, she really needs to hear this.
我瞭解，但是在你那樣做之前 她真的需要先聽我說
Okay.
好的
- Would you care for my seat as well? - Actually, yeah, that'd be great.
-你要坐我的座位嗎？ -事實上會很好
Well, that's fair, you've had a long trip.
很公平，你一路這麼遠趕來
Phoebe, I love you.
菲比，我愛你
I've missed you so much these last few months.
我過去幾個月非常思念你
I thought we were apart for a good reason..
我原以為我們分開是有好理由的
but I realized that there was no reason good enough..
但是我發現根本沒有夠好的理由…
to keep me from spending the rest of my life with you.
能夠讓我不與你共度下半輩子
Kind of steps on the toes of what I was going to say.
有點毀了我將要說的話
I'm sorry, David, but she really has to know this.
抱歉，大衛 但是她真的有需要知道這些
All right, but after this, I want to see you outside.
好的，但是之後 我要在外面跟你單挑
If it stops raining.
如果外面停止下雨的話
You're the most incredible woman I've ever met.
你是我遇過最不可思議的女人
How could I lose you? Now, I don't actually have a ring.
我怎麼能夠失去你呢？ 我現在並沒有戒指
- I have a ring. - I wouldn't brag about that, big guy.
-我有戒指 -我不會在這時候炫耀，老兄
But, Phoebe..
但是，菲比…
will you marry me?
你願意嫁給我嗎？
No.
不
I love you, but I never needed a proposal from you.
我愛你，但是我從不需要你求婚
I just needed to know we were headed somewhere.
我只需要知道我們之間是有發展的
- That we had a future. - We can have any future you want.
-我們是有未來的 -我們可以有任何你想要的未來
Okay, well, I'm gonna take off.
好的，我要走了
David, I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
大衛，我很抱歉，我好抱歉
Just so I know, if I had asked first..?
讓我知道一下，如果我先問了？
Yeah, I might have said yes, but that would've been wrong.
我有可能會答應，但是那是不對的
Please, you don't have to explain.
你不用解釋，沒關係
I mean, perhaps if I hadn't gone to Minsk..
我是說 如果我當初沒有去明斯克…
things would have worked out for us, and I wouldn't have ruined my career.
我們之間可能就沒問題了 而我也不會毀了我的事業
Or lost that toe to frostbite.
或是因凍瘡而失去那隻腳趾
It was a good trip.
那是趟好旅程
- Is it okay if I hug you now? - Oh, yes.
-我現在可以擁抱你嗎？ -喔，可以
Because of our meddling! All right?
就是因為我們的多管閒事，好嗎？
Oh, isn't this nice? It's so quiet. I could just lie here all day.
這樣不是很好嗎？如此安靜 我可以整天都躺在這裡
Oh, I know.
我知道
- Open your drapes! Open your drapes! - So glad we got adjoining rooms.
-打開窗簾！打開窗簾！ -我們的房間是相通的還真不錯呢
- The sun is out! - Hey! Remember when I had corneas?
-太陽出來了！ -嘿！記得我看得到的時候嗎？
Go to the pool and reserve chairs.
趕快去游泳池佔位子
- I will get the magazines and the lotion. - Ladies? Ross' speech is in 45 minutes.
-我會拿雜誌跟防曬乳液 -羅斯的演講再四十五分就開始了
- No! - Damn it!
-不！ -該死的！
Walls are pretty thin, guys.
牆壁很薄的，你們這些人
"Then we have to weigh the data from recent MRI scans and DNA testing..
我們必須考量最近磁共振造影資料 與去氧核糖核酸測試資料…
which call into question information gathered from years of carbon dating."
而這些對多年來的碳年代 測定資料收集方式形成了一些疑點
Look at the woman sitting out by the pool getting tan.
瞧瞧那個坐在游泳池畔 享受日光浴的女人
She's all leathery and wrinkled. I'm so jealous!
她的皮都有皺紋了，我真是忌妒！
"Finally, factor in the profusion of new species recently discovered.
最後， 最近有許多豐富新物種的發現
Giganotosaurus.
巨獸龍
- Argentinosaurus." - Not to mention Coldsaurus.
-阿根廷龍 -更不用提冷龍
"And that's just the herbivores. I'm not even gonna discuss the carnivores.
而這些只是草食性的 我還沒有要提到肉食性的
Their heads are already too big.
他們的頭都已經是太大了
Which is ironic, considering their stunted cerebral development."
這是蠻諷刺的 因為他們的大腦卻是發育不良的
Really?
真的嗎？
"But all kidding aside, in much the same way..
但是撇開玩笑不談，這是相同於…
that Homo ergaster is thought to be a separate species from Homo erectus.."
匠人曾被認為是直立人（音近勃起）的 另一個分支
- What? - He said "erectus."
-什麼？ -他說「直立人」
- You're kidding, right? - No, he really said it.
-你在開玩笑嗎？ -不，他是真的那樣說
"And while there are certainly vast differences..
而當然有許多很大的差異…
between these Mesozoic fossils and the example of Homo erectus.."
介於這些中生代化石 跟此直立人例子
Erectus?
勃起？
- Homo. - Right.
-同性戀（音同人屬） -沒錯
"In a very real way, we can bring the Mesozoic Era into the 21st century."
「已非常真實的方式，我們可以 將中生代時期帶入二十一世紀」
Thank you.
謝謝
- Really great. - Oh, thanks, guys.
-真的很棒 -謝謝你們
I thought it was wonderful. Jarvis Oberblau. Cornell.
我認為很精采，我是傑維斯歐伯勞 康乃爾大學
I mean, the ideas you put forth, and from someone so young and..
你突顯出來的議題 尤其是你是這樣的年輕而且…
Okay, now we're just holding hands.
好的，現在我們只是在握著手
Alrighty. We're gonna hit the beach. That was really great.
好的，我們要去海灘了 演講真的很棒
- Oh, thank you. - Yeah. Oh, and so funny.
-謝謝 -是啊，而且很有趣
- Take it easy. - All right, thanks. Thanks so much.
-放輕鬆點 -好的，謝謝，非常謝謝
I can't tell you how much it means that you were here.
我無法告訴你 你們在此對我意義有多大
You kidding? We wouldn't have missed it.
你在開玩笑嗎？我們不可能會錯過的
I'm back.
我回來了
Okay. Well, excuse me?
好的，失陪一下好嗎？
- Well? - You were incredible.
-怎麼樣？ -你真是不可思議
You blew them away.
你完全迷住了他們了
I can't tell you how great it was to look in the crowd and see your face.
我無法告訴你在人群中 看到你的臉有多棒
I mean, did you know you were mouthing the words along with me?
我是說 你知道你嘴巴在跟著我念嗎？
- I was not. - No, it's okay.
-我沒有 -不，沒關係
It made me feel like a rock star.
那讓我覺得很像搖滾巨星
Oh, my God. I'm your groupie.
我的天啊 我跟你研究的東西是一樣的
Hey, I better not find you naked in my hotel room.
我最好不要在房間裡 發現你脫光光喔
Look, I took it too far.
哎呀，我又扯太遠了
Hey, I thought you were going to the beach.
我以為你要去海灘
- It's raining again. - What?
-又在下雨了 -什麼？
Would you look at that.
你瞧瞧吧
The only time the sun comes out the whole weekend..
這星期以來 唯一有太陽的時候…
is the one hour I'm giving my speech.
就是我在演講的那個小時
Someone up there likes me.
那上頭的某人還真喜歡我
But people down here are pissed.
但是下面的一些人都氣死了
I can't believe it's raining again. It's so unfair.
我不敢相信又在下雨了，真是不公平
Well, on the bright side, now we won't have to see..
往好處想就是我們不用看到…
all these paleontologists with their shirts off.
那些古生物學家脫掉上衣
Not you guys.
不是你們
You've got it going on.
你們還不錯
- What will we do today? - They have a game room downstairs.
-我們今天要做什麼呢？ -他們樓下有遊戲間
They have Ping-Pong and stuff.
有兵乓球還有其他的東西
Ping-Pong? Honey, they have Ping-Pong.
乒乓球？親愛的，他們有乒乓球耶
- Let's play. - I don't think so.
-我們來玩 -我想不好
- Why not? - You know how competitive you get.
-為什麼不要？ -你知道你得失心很重的
And while I say it's cute, others disagree, and I'm lying.
我以前說那樣很可愛，可是 別人都不同意，而且我在說謊
- I'm not always that bad. - Oh, yeah?
-我又不是永遠都那樣糟糕 -是嗎？
What happened when we played last time?
我們上次玩的時候發生什麼事呢？
I punched you.
我揍了你
- And? - Phoebe.
-還有呢？ -還有菲比
- And? - I clunked your heads together.
-還有呢？ -我把你們的頭撞在一起
- There you are. - Hey. Listen.
-你在這裡 -嘿，聽著
As soon as it stops raining, we have got to go snorkeling.
只要一停止下雨 我們一定要去浮潛
Some kid told me about this sea turtle. If you blow bubbles in his face..
有個小孩告訴我有海龜 如果你對著他的臉吹氣泡…
he chases you.
他會追著你跑喔
I'm sorry, I can't. I'm running a discussion group all afternoon.
我很抱歉，我不能去 我整個下午都要主持一個討論組
That's okay. I'll find someone else to do it.
沒關係，我找別人去好了
I'd do it alone, but..
我是可以一個人去，但是…
I don't know what happens if the sea turtle catches you.
我不知道海龜 如果抓到我會發生什麼事
You know, I feel so bad.
我覺得很糟糕
I haven't seen you this whole trip. Especially last night..
我整趟旅途都沒有跟你在一起 尤其是昨晚…
Don't worry about it. It was fine. I had the best time with Rachel.
不用擔心，沒關係 我跟瑞秋玩的很開心
I just felt bad for you, stuck in that room working on Ross' speech.
我只是為你難過 跟羅斯關在房間裡趕演講稿
Actually, it turned out to be a lot of fun.
事實上，結果還蠻好玩的
Oh, well, at least we're both having fun, right?
那至少我們都過得很愉快，不是嗎？
- Is it weird that it's not with each other? - Yeah.
-我們不在一起卻很快樂，很怪吧？ -是啊
A little bit, yeah.
有一點，是啊
I think we need to talk.
我想我們需要談談
Yeah, I think we do.
是啊，我想我們是需要
About what?
談什麼呢？
- Come on, you guys, it'll be fun! - All right.
-別這樣，會很好玩的啦！ -好啦
- I'll play if we don't keep score. - Well, then how do we know who wins?
-不計分我才要玩 -那我們怎麼知道誰贏呢？
- Nobody wins. - So we're just four losers. Super.
-沒有人會贏 -所以我們是四個輸家，太好了
- Well, I'm not playing with her. - I'm out.
-我不要跟她玩 -我不要玩了
- I'll play you. - Okay.
-我跟你玩 -好的
- You don't know what you're doing. - She gets crazy.
-你不知道你在做什麼 -她會很瘋狂的
This scar? That's from Pictionary.
這個疤痕是從猜字遊戲來的
I think I'll be all right.
我想我會沒事的
- You want to volley a bit for serve? - Sure, if you want to.
-你想要先熱身一下嗎？ -當然，如果你想要的話
Oh, by the way, I'm awesome.
對了，我很厲害的
Oh, dear God, there's two of them.
親愛的上帝，他們倆是一樣的
- You ready to play? - Hell, yeah.
-你準備好要玩了嗎？ -當然了
- Did you know this about him? - No idea. I thought he was soft like you.
-你有看過他這一面嗎？ -沒有，我以為他跟你一樣軟弱
- Want to make it more interesting? - How much you thinking?
-想要更好玩點嗎？ -你想要多少呢？
- Ten bucks a game? - Make it 50.
-十塊錢一局嗎？ -加到五十塊錢好了
- I'll make it 100. - One thousand..
-我加到一百塊錢 -一千…
Okay!
好了！
We'll flip to see who goes first. You got a quarter?
我們擲銅板來決定誰先開球 你有銅板嗎？
No. Either of you girls got a quarter?
沒有，你們兩個女生誰有銅板呢？
Honey, try to focus the trash talk on him.
親愛的，把這種罵人的話 都用到他身上
- Monica, you call it. - Heads. No, tails! Heads!
-摩妮卡，你來猜 -正面，不，背面！正面！
- Tails. - Oh, what are the chances?
-背面 -機率有這樣低嗎？
- My point! - Oh, no, I don't think so.
-我得分！ -不，我可不這麼認為
Standard rules: If at any time a player uses his nonracket-bearing hand..
根據標準法規定，若參賽者 在任何時間將沒握球拍的手…
to touch the playing surface, he or she forfeits the point.
碰觸到球桌表面，將不算得分
He was a lawyer.
他曾經是律師
All the East Coast is having beautiful weather.
東岸的天氣十分良好
In New York, it's 72 and sunny.
在紐約是華氏七十二度 而且陽光普照
Weather bitch.
氣象婊子
It's open.
門沒鎖
- Hi, Joe. - Hey.
-嗨，喬伊 -嘿
- What? Is everything okay? - Charlie and I broke up.
-怎麼了？一切都還好嗎？ -查莉跟我分手了
No. Why?
不，為什麼？
Well, she said we have nothing in common.
嗯，她說我們沒有任何共同點
That's crazy.
這真是胡說
No, it's not. We have nothing in common.
不，是真的，我們沒有任何共同點
- Yeah, that's true. - Yeah.
-是啊，沒錯 -是啊
I mean, she should be with someone more like Ross.
她應該跟像是羅斯那樣的人在一起
You know, I mean he uses all those big words too.
你知道的 他也會用那些很難的字眼
- Man, smart people are dull. - Well, hey!
-天啊，聰明的人真是無趣 -嗯，是啊！
Okay, Rach.
好了，瑞秋
I feel so stupid, you know? Why do I keep going after the wrong girls?
我覺得好蠢，你知道嗎？為什麼我一直 都喜歡不適合我的女生呢？
- What are you talking about? - Oh, come on.
-你在說什麼呢？ -喔，少來了
I mean, there's you, then there's Charlie. It's like.. What the hell's my problem?
我是說，有你，然後是查莉 這就像是…我到底是哪根筋不對呢？
I just..
我只是…
Okay. Maybe you're not always going after the wrong girl.
或許你並沒有都跟 不適合你的女生一起
I'm telling you, Rach, Charlie is not right for me.
我告訴你，瑞秋 查莉並不適合我
- I'm not talking about her. - Well, then, who?
-我不是在說她 -是喔，那是誰呢？
The waitress I went out with last month?
那個我上個月約過的女服務生嗎？
- You know what? Forget it. - No, no, no, no.
-你知道嗎？算了 -不…
- Who are you talking about? - No, I don't..
-你是在說誰呢？ -不，我不…
I actually don't know who I'm talking about, so..
事實上我並不知道 我在說什麼，所以…
- Okay. - Yeah.
-好的 -嗯
Well, I'm gonna go see if I can get a room for tonight.
我要去看看有沒有辦法 再訂到另一間房間
- And I'll see you later. - Yeah, sure. Okay.
-待會見 -是啊，好的
- You like me? - Okay.
-你喜歡我？ -好吧
- Let's not make a big thing about this. - It's a huge thing!
-我們不要過度渲染這件事 -這是一件大事！
Okay, not working with me, Joe.
你很不合作喔，喬伊
Look, here's the thing. Lately, I have been having thoughts.
聽著，事情事這樣的 最近，我有些想法
Musings, if you will.
應該說是冥想
- Well, for how long? - Oh, only like a month.
-多久了呢？ -大概只有一個月
- A month? - Well..
-一個月？ -嗯…
Dial it down. Listen, maybe they're crazy thoughts, but sometimes I do.
小聲點，或許只是一些瘋狂的想法 但是有時候我就是會想啊
I have been thinking about, you know, us.
我一直在想我們之間的可能性
- Okay, dial it up a little. - Oh, you're right. Okay.
-好的，現在音調提高一點 -你說的對，好的
- I just have a question. - Shoot.
-我只有一個問題 -該死
- What the hell are you doing? - I'm not trying to do anything.
-你倒底是在做什麼？ -我試著不要做任何事
It's just, we have such a good time when we're together, you know?
只是當我們在一起時非常地快樂 你知道嗎？
And I mean, aren't you just a little curious what it would be like?
你難道都沒有好奇過 那會是怎樣嗎？
Am I curious? I mean, I'm as curious as..
我好奇過？我就跟…
George!
喬治一樣好奇！
- Who? - Curious George!
-誰？ -好奇喬治阿！
You know, the monkey and the guy with the yellow hat.
那隻猴子還有那個戴黃帽的男人
- Of course. I remember. - He had a paper route.
-我當然記得 -他還有個紙路線圖
Yeah, he did.
是啊，沒錯
- See, this is what I'm talking about. - No, I know. We're great!
-這就是我說的 -我知道，我們棒透了！
But, Rach, no, this can't happen.
但是瑞秋，不，不能這樣的
Can't it just happen a little bit?
不能有一點點機會嗎？
- No! It can't happen at all! - Why not?
-不！一點也不行 -為什麼不行？
Because, look, no one wants this to happen more than me, okay?
我最希望事情是這樣了，好嗎？
I have gone over this moment in my head 100 times..
我在我腦海中已經幻想過 這情節一百次了
and not once did I ever say no.
而且我從沒拒絕過
I couldn't do it to Ross.
我不能這樣對羅斯
- But that wasn't gonna stop you before. - I know. I know..
-但之前卻不是這樣 -我知道…
but I've thought about it a lot since then, and it just wouldn't be right.
但是在那之後我想了很多 這是不對的
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry too.
我也很抱歉
- Oh, God, I shouldn't have said anything. - No, no.
-天啊，我不應該說出來的 -不…
No, no, no, no. Hey, we'll be fine.
別這樣，我們沒事的
- Like you said, it's no big deal. - It's not a big deal.
-就像你所說的，這沒有什麼 -沒錯
- No big deal. - It's so not a big deal.
-沒有什麼 -真的是沒有什麼
- I'll see you later. All right, hey. - Okay, great.
-待會見，好囉 -好的，太好了
Okay..
好的…
Oh, I'm sorry, I think.. I think that may have missed the table.
真抱歉喔，我想… 我想那可能沒有碰到桌面
- Oh, do you? - Yeah.
-是嗎？ -是的
- Do you? - Yeah.
- Do you? - Yeah!
-是嗎？ -是的！
- You really find this attractive on him? - Oh, yeah.
-你真的認為他這樣很有魅力嗎？ -是的
Are you telling me you're not even a little turned on by Monica right now?
你要告訴我你現在沒有 被摩妮卡撩的心癢癢的？
This is the first time in our marriage that I've felt like the more attractive one.
這是婚後我第一次覺得 我是比較有魅力的那一個
All right, come on, Mike. You can beat her.
好了，加油，麥克，你可以打敗她的
Knock that dog off her head.
把她打的落花流水
- Damn it! - I sleep with him!
-該死的！ -我跟他上床喔！
- Game point. - Don't get too cocky.
-關鍵點 -別太驕傲
Remember, I won the last one.
記住上次是我贏的
Oh, by the way, how did that feel, losing to a girl?
喔，對了 輸給一個女生感覺如何呢？
You should look in the mirror before you call yourself that.
你應該先照照鏡子再這樣說
- No! No! No! - And that's how it's done.
-不！不！不！ -而就是這樣結束了
Okey-dokey.
好了
You've each won a game, and I've lost what's felt like a year of my life.
你們都各贏了一局 而我感覺好像是失去了一年的生命
Everybody goes home a winner.
每個人都可以跟一個贏家回家
- Best of three? - That's what I'm thinking.
-三戰兩勝？ -我就是這樣想
Should I use my invisibility to fight crime or for evil?
我應該運用我的隱形術 來打擊罪犯或是惡魔？
- Serve the ball, chump. - "Serve the ball, chump."
-開球吧，木頭人 -「開球吧，木頭人」
Okay, better comebacks, Mike. Better comebacks.
好的，重披戰袍會更好，麥克 重披戰袍會更好
I got it!
我來接！
I'm fine, by the way!
我沒事！
I'm just saying, I have a cabin in the Adirondacks.
我是說我在阿爾剛金有間小木屋
If you ever want to get away from the city, well, that'd be..
如果你有想要遠離塵囂 那會是…
just nifty.
很不錯的
Well, I've kind of got a lot on my plate right now.
嗯，我現在事情是蠻多的
Not that I wouldn't love a weekend in the country with a strange man.
不是說我不喜歡 跟陌生男人到鄉間度週末
- Jarvis? - Oh, you're back.
-傑維斯？ -喔，你回來了
- This is my wife, Nancy. - Well, get out!
-這是我老婆，南西 -少來了！
- Ross? Can I talk to you for a minute? - Yes, please.
-羅斯，我可以跟你談談嗎？ -當然了
Is he still looking at me?
他還在看我嗎？
Yes.
是的
- Still? - Yes.
-還在看嗎？ -是的
And his wife's kind of looking at me.
而他老婆好像是在看我
So, what's going on?
發生什麼事呢？
Well, Joey and I broke up.
嗯，喬伊跟我分手了
- Oh, my God. What happened? - Joey is a great guy..
-我的天啊，發生了什麼事？ -喬伊是個好男人
but we're just.. We're so different.
但是我們就是… 我們很不一樣了
I mean, like, during your speech, he kept laughing at "Homo erectus."
就像是在你演講的時候 他一直在笑「直立人」
I knew that was him!
我就知道是他！
Anyway, I just.. I think it's for the best.
反正，我只是… 我想這樣是最好的
- Hey. Hey, you okay? - I guess.
-嘿，你還好嗎？ -還好
There was..
還有…
There was another reason that I thought it was time to end it with Joey.
還有另外一個原因 讓我跟喬伊分手的
I started to realize that I was having feelings for someone else.
我開始發覺 我對另外一個人有感覺
Okay, Geller. Last day of the conference.
好的，蓋勒，研討會的最後一天了
You know what happens to the keynote speaker.
你知道主講人會被怎樣的
Professor Klarik, we're in the middle of a conversation here.
克雷克教授，我們正在談話當中
- Can't you throw him in the pool later? - Or we could throw you both in now.
-不能等會再丟他進游泳池嗎？ -或是把你們倆都丟進去
Okay, gentlemen, please. Aren't we a little old for this?
男士們，拜託，我們會不會太老了呢？
I mean, we're scientists, all right? We're academics..
我是說我們是科學家，好嗎？ 我們都有學術素養
and most importantly, you will have to catch us first.
而且最重要的 你們必須要先捉住我們
Go! Go! Go!
跑！跑！跑！
Okay, so it's tied again, 41 to 41.
好的，又平手了，四十一比四十一
- Okay, look, enough is enough. - No.
-好的，聽著，夠了 -不
- I just have two more points to beat him. - Monica, that was also true an hour ago!
-我剩下兩分就可以打敗他了 -摩妮卡，一小時前你就這樣說了！
I mean, please, look at you.
拜託，瞧瞧你自己
Your hand is blistered, you can barely stand, your hair is inexplicable!
你的手都起水泡了，你連站都站不住 你的頭髮真是莫名奇妙！
Phoebe, talk to Mike. Help me out.
菲比，去跟麥克說，幫忙我一下
Mike, you win this, you will get the best sex you've ever had in your whole life.
麥克，只要你贏，你將會享受到 你從未享受過的性愛
I say to fight crime.
好像是打擊罪犯比較好
You didn't see us!
你沒有看到我們！
Monica?
摩妮卡？
You've already proven you're just as good as he is.
你已經證明你跟他一樣好了
We missed our dinner reservations, so let's just go upstairs..
我們已經錯過晚餐預約 所以我們就上樓去…
order room service, take a shower and shave your head!
點客房服務，洗個澡 然後剃光你的頭髮！
I can't just walk away. I've put in four hours.
我不能這樣走掉 我已經投入四小時了
You knew this about me when you married me.
當你娶我的時候 你就知道我是這樣的
You agreed to take me in sickness and in health.
你答應無論我生病 或是健康都要照顧我的
Well, this is my sickness!
這就是我的病！
- What about the obsessive cleaning? - That's just good sense.
-那潔癖呢？ -那只是好習慣
- You okay? - No, honey, I'm okay.
-你還好嗎？ -親愛的，我還好
Shake it off. Oh, no shaking. No shaking. No shaking.
甩一甩，哎，不能甩 不能甩，不能甩
Oh, my God. I can't play.
我的天，我不能玩了
- So you forfeit? - Mike wins?
-所以你要棄權？ -麥克贏了嗎？
I can't believe it. I lost.
我不敢相信，我輸了
- No, you didn't. - What?
-不，你沒有 -什麼？
- Because I'm gonna play for you. - You can't do that.
-因為我要幫你玩 -你不能這樣做
It's okay. I don't care which of them I beat.
沒關係，我不在乎 到底是打敗他們其中哪個
Okay, we're taking that paddle home, mister.
好的，我們要把 那個球拍帶回家，先生
- Honey, you don't have to do this. - Yes, I do.
-親愛的，你沒有必要這樣做 -是的，我有必要
I may not understand why you have to win so badly..
我或許無法理解 你為什麼一定要贏…
but if it's important to you, it's important to me.
但是如果這對你很重要 對我就很重要
Because I love you.
因為我愛你
But you suck.
但是你很遜阿
You're welcome, sweetheart.
不客氣，甜心
All right, let's get this over with. Sudden death.
好的，我們快玩吧，快點受死
- Whoever wins this point, wins. - Okay.
-贏得這一分的人就算贏了 -好的
- Oh, my God. You're good. - It's like watching porn.
-天啊，你真棒 -這就像是看色情片一樣
And that's how it's done.
而這就是這樣結束的
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. That was so amazing.
我的天啊… 這實在太驚人了
Well, when did you..?
嗯，你是何時…
Hold on, I almost forgot. Loser.
等等，我差點忘了，失敗者
- When did you stop sucking? - I never sucked. I just didn't want you..
-你是什麼時候開始不遜的？ -我從來就不遜，我只是不想讓你…
- to know how good I was. - Why?
-知道我有多棒 -為什麼？
- I don't know. - Well, this is so great.
-我不知道 -這真是太棒了
- Now we can enter doubles tournaments. - That's why.
-現在我們可以參加雙打比賽了 -這就是為什麼
- They still looking for us? - Yeah.
-他們還在找我們嗎？ -是的
The bartender said they split up into two search parties.
酒保說他們分成兩組搜索隊伍
The herbivores and the carnivores.
草食性組跟肉食性組
You know, we, as a group, are not the coolest.
我們這一組並不是最酷的
Oh, look out.
喔，小心
- I don't think they saw us. - I don't think they did.
-我想他們沒有看到我們 -沒錯
You know, for a bunch of researchers, they sure don't look very carefully.
身為研究家 他們並沒有很認真的探索
So I started to tell you something earlier.
我剛剛要開始告訴你一些事
There was another reason that I realized it was time to end it with Joey.
還有其他的原因 讓我跟喬伊分手的
I kind of realized I was starting to have feelings..
我有點驚覺到我開始對某人…
for someone else.
有一些感覺
And can I ask who?
我可以問是誰嗎？
I think you know.
我想你知道是誰
I think I know too, but I've been really wrong about this stuff in the past, so..
我想我也是，但過去我對這種事的判斷 都是錯的，所以…
- I'm sorry, we can't. - All right. All right.
-我很抱歉，我們不能 -好的，好的
I mean, you just went out with my best friend, you know?
我是說 你才剛跟我最好的朋友交往過
I just think it would be a really, really bad idea.
我只是認為這會是個很不好的主意
Or not. I mean..
或許不會，我是說…
What?
什麼？